<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ads type="array">
<ad><id>1</id><title>2011 Dodge Grand Caravan SE</title><body>2011 Dodge Grand Caravan SE Call To contact someone for more information on this vehicle, or to see more of our ads on KIJIJI, please refer to the &quot;Posted Contact Information&quot; on the top right hand ...</body><price>19900</price><pdate>2012/06/24</pdate></ad>
<ad><id>2</id><title>2004 Toyota 4Runner V6</title><body>2004 Toyota 4Runner V6 $14,900 To contact someone for more information on this vehicle, or to see more of our ads on KIJIJI, please refer to the &quot;Posted Contact Information&quot; on the top right hand ...</body><price>14900</price><pdate>2012/05/27</pdate></ad>
<ad><id>3</id><title>Instrumentation Technician/Electrician AT LABATT BREWERIES</title><body>Labatt Breweries of Canada is seeking an Instrumentation Technician/Electrician in our Edmonton Brewery Perform various maintenance activities from corrective to preventive with the objective to ...</body><price></price><pdate>2013/02/28</pdate></ad>
<ad><id>4</id><title>***VERY CLEAN SPORT UTILITY***</title><body>2006 Prairie Team Green 700 - Paid 10,500.00 new PowerMadd Hand guards - 100.00 with mounts Rox 3.5&quot; Pivoting Risers With Dash Clamps - 100.00 ODI Grips With Plugs and Lock Rings - 55.00 Fasst Flexx ...</body><price>7600</price><pdate>2013/02/26</pdate></ad>
<ad><id>5</id><title>Cleaner Evenings</title><body>Cleaner part time evenings for Stony Plain and Spruce Grove. Experience and ability to obtain a clean criminal record check required. We provide all equipment. Alliance Building Maintenance.</body><price></price><pdate>2013/03/05</pdate></ad>
<ad><id>6</id><title>2006 Dodge Ram 2500 Laramie</title><body>Crossline Kingsway 2006 Dodge Ram 2500 Laramie Very nice unit! Professionally detailed and looks new inside out. Air conditioning, cd player and much more.2 inch Lifted with really nice rims. ...</body><price>16995</price><pdate>2012/02/17</pdate></ad>
<ad><id>7</id><title>Going skiing</title><body>I&apos;m looking to rent skiing stuff for my skiing trip this weekend for I have no ski gear and I&apos;m not going out to buy this gear for a once a year thing...so .looking for everything:</body><price></price><pdate>2012/05/26</pdate></ad>
<ad><id>8</id><title>Cleaner Evenings</title><body>Cleaner part time evenings for Stony Plain and Spruce Grove. Experience and ability to obtain a clean criminal record check required. We provide all equipment. Alliance Building Maintenance.</body><price></price><pdate>2012/06/19</pdate></ad>
<ad><id>9</id><title>Looking for a one bedroom apart in the Capilano Mall area</title><body>Hello! I’m a quiet, mature professional female, looking for a one bedroom apartment in the vicinity or with easy access to the Capilano Mall area. I would prefer an all in rent but I’m flexible to ...</body><price>900</price><pdate>2013/01/08</pdate></ad>
<ad><id>10</id><title>HEAVY DUTY MECHANIC REQUIRED!!</title><body>Heavy duty mechanic required to take over fleet maintenance and manage our shop. Work with a company that has over 54 years in the transport industry. Ryl Construction is a privately owned and ...</body><price></price><pdate>2012/01/26</pdate></ad>
</ads>
